i like my life it's good i live in a
small town anyone else live in a small
town
a couple of years nice yeah i like being
in a small town there's no rush hour
people always think there's rush hour
but there's nothing okay i'm from a
small farming town the closest thing we
have to rush hour is if you like drive
towards another town
during the harvest
because like all the combines
are just on the road for some reason
and they'll always pull over to be nice
it's like you're 40 feet wide dude that
is helping nobody
and turn your blade off you're making
everyone nervous
what happened to sheila she was
harvested no
she was so nice she was so nice but now
she is delicious
her mature trees couldn't save her
i love small towns because it's just a
different energy in small towns i one
time witnessed a fight at my local
thrift store and i shall tell you the
tale
so i'm in there and i'm thrifting that's
what i'm doing in there and i heard a
kerfuffle
you do not have that word in the united
states of america but i trust you to
figure it out vis-a-vis context
so i heard a kerfuffle i did not know
what the kerfuffle was but i knew there
was kerfuffing
i got to the till and it was me a woman
in front of me and then
the kerfuffle
and she was upset because she was
purchasing a two-piece bathing suit
let's just pause right there
yes you can purchase a bathing suit at
your local thrift store
but you shouldn't okay
if you do listen they wash it you still
need to bleach it do you understand what
i'm saying
just trying to help
so she was upset because the tag said
1.25 but what she did not realize was
that it was a dollar 25
per piece
and this was if you recall
a
two-piece bringing the grand total to
2.50
and she was having none of it
i will never forget in all my life i
heard her say well maybe in the city
where in the city are you finding a
bathing suit for two dollars and fifty
cents
if you find a bathing suit in a dumpster
you still leave five bucks it's a
bathing suit
and i'll be honest with you i was
annoyed because the money does not go to
some conglomerate at the top of the food
chain it goes to local charities around
our community and it's a dollar
twenty-five
i did not say any of that because i am a
coward
[Laughter]
woman in front of me
not a coward
[Laughter]
brave woman
she spoke up she goes oh come on it's
only a dollar
and twenty-five kerfuffer looks at her
and she says
this is none of your concern
[Music]
and then the brave woman gestures to me
and she goes well i think it is our
concern i'm like leave me out of this
you started it you finish it
and then something shifted in the
kerfer's eyes she's turned to the brave
woman and she said you just stay out of
this old lady
and that is wrong
that is wrong for two reasons number one
you do not call somebody old and
therefore invalidate them
and second of all
they were both old
these were two old ladies
fighting over a bathing suit at the
local thrift store would you like to
know what happens when you call an old
lady an old lady i shall tell you she
moved her shopping cart to one side
advanced on the first woman and straight
up shoves her
immediately all the adrenaline starts
pumping through my body i'm like let's
go we doing this come on
i'll separate you bring your bounce down
bam
i didn't do that i didn't do that what i
actually did was this
that's what i did that's my move
that's my whole stick no please don't
stop the curve of me
i was still in charge of that situation
it was fine
and then the keffer she gets all
frazzled she storms out of there i don't
know if she like paid for the whole
bathing suit maybe she just took half of
the bathing suit with her but she got
out of there and then the best bit
happened
the brave woman looks over at me and she
says
well
maybe i should just dye my hair brown
[Laughter]
i'm still trying to figure that one out
like
was she making fun of the first lady's
hair
was she saying she didn't want to be
called old anymore
or most likely
did she realize
she just physically assaulted somebody
in a public space
and she needed to lay low for a while
i tell some jokes i defuse the tension a
little bit i go to my car i tell my wife
she doesn't even believe me of course
she doesn't would you no
and if you're from a small town you'll
get this next part we drove from the
thrift store
to the grocery store i walked in i saw a
friend of mine behind the counter who
loves stories like this so with the
biggest smile on my face i told her the
whole tale from beginning to end and she
had already heard the story
how fast does news travel in a small
town faster than a mazda 3 apparently
you